

# SABRA AKHAVAN

### Front-end developer

I am a 23-year-old self-thoughted front-end developer with experience in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I am passionate about creating intuitive and visually appealing web applications that meet client needs. I am committed to continuous learning and growth in the ever-evolving field of web development.

#### contact



+98-921-405-3184



sabraxavan@gmail.com



www.sabraakhavan.ir



Iran, Guilan, Rasht

### language

Persian English Deutsch

### education

### bachelor of Genetics

2020 - 2023

Guilan university

## work experience

### Junior developer

2022-2023

Learned and worked at the same time at Pejvak co.

#### freelancer

2023-now

#### skills

- HTML, CSS, SASS, BEM
- Bootstrap, tailwind
- JavaScript
- Git
- React
- Responsive Styling
- Debugging
- Computer Literacy
- Strong Communication
- >Excellent Problem-solving
- Adobes: Ps, Ai, Lr, Pr

### interest

Painting, Playing games, Travelling, reading